<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Sierra Data Systems</title>
    <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Sierra Data Systems</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 09:02:26 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Productivity Killer</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/big-productivity-killer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 09:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/big-productivity-killer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et. Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Maecenas sed diam eget risus varius blandit sit amet non magna. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 09:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
 Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/terms-of-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 09:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/terms-of-service/</guid>
      <description>1. Terms By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get the details on WMS</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/details-about-wms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 19:02:32 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/details-about-wms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Donec sed odio dui. Maecenas faucibus mollis interdum. Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum.
Nullam id dolor id nibh ultricies vehicula ut id elit. Cras justo odio, dapibus ac facilisis in, egestas eget quam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of the POD</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/power-of-the-pod/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 09:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/power-of-the-pod/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Duis mollis, est non commodo luctus, nisi erat porttitor ligula, eget lacinia odio sem nec elit. Vestibulum id ligula porta felis euismod semper. Fusce dapibus, tellus ac cursus commodo, tortor mauris condimentum nibh, ut fermentum massa justo sit amet risus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The advantages of tracking containers.</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/advantages-of-container-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 09:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/advantages-of-container-tracking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et. Curabitur blandit tempus porttitor. Donec ullamcorper nulla non metus auctor fringilla. Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet. Integer posuere erat a ante venenatis dapibus posuere velit aliquet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why GPS is Really Great</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/gps-really-great/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 09:02:26 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/blog/gps-really-great/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et. Aenean eu leo quam. Pellentesque ornare sem lacinia quam venenatis vestibulum. Maecenas sed diam eget risus varius blandit sit amet non magna. Nullam quis risus eget urna mollis ornare vel eu leo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asset Tracking</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/solutions/asset-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/solutions/asset-tracking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced business world, keeping track of all the moving pieces can be increasingly frustrating and expensive. Accurately watching over the location, possession and movement of valuable company assets can be the difference in finishing a job on time or missing costly deadlines. From hospitals to construction sites, facility management, and equipment sales, forward-thinking companies are looking for better ways to track valuable equipment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dispatching</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/dispatching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/dispatching/</guid>
      <description>To keep your organization running smoothly, it is critical to schedule and properly dispatch your personnel. Manual dispatching systems can quickly become crippled by various service requests, changes to employee schedules, and frequent ad-hoc requests. By automating your dispatching needs your mobile workforce is better equipped to respond to ongoing work and maintain the responsive service times your customers expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driver Management</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/driver-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/driver-management/</guid>
      <description>Nothing ruins an efficient day like forgotten supplies or neglected safety checks. Take advantage of tailored mobile workflows and GPS management to keep your fleet moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Icons Demo</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/icons-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/icons-demo/</guid>
      <description>This is the current list of Font-Awesome icons we are using. If there is an icon that you wish to use, let me know and I will add it to our list. You can find a comprehensive list of available icons on the Font Awesome website: Free Set and Pro Set</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last-Mile</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/solutions/last-mile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/solutions/last-mile/</guid>
      <description>You have heard it said, &amp;ldquo;it is not how you start, but how you finish.&amp;rdquo; In the world of supply chain logistics, this is undoubtedly the case. The final stretch of the delivery process is no time to coast.
Along with being a key to customer satisfaction, last mile delivery can be the most expensive and time-consuming part of the entire shipping process. Today&amp;rsquo;s end-customer is more mobile savvy and less patient than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/solutions/manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/solutions/manufacturing/</guid>
      <description>Efficiency within the production and manufacturing industry is the pivotal difference in profitability and customer satisfaction. From receiving the initial order to moving through the shop floor and onto the loading dock, manufacturing companies must have a realistic understanding of their actual production process.
The transformative potential of enterprise mobility within the manufacturing industry is inescapable. But for many mid-sized companies, an investment into a full-scale Warehouse Management System (WMS) is cost prohibitive and goes beyond the pressing need to have a cohesive strategy tying together the sales order, production, staging, kitting, and shipment process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Company is the best</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/company/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proof of Delivery</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/proof-of-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/proof-of-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are transporting people, medical supplies or delivering perishable food, you can’t afford to waste time, money or resources. Leverage a mobile solution that gives you the answers you need to oversee the handling of all items efficiently and accurately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reporting</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/reporting/</guid>
      <description>The most successful companies know that being held captive by the tyranny of the urgent rarely produces quality service and efficient operations. Taking advantage of our reporting features allows you to step back and evaluate critical operational indicators and set your team up for greater success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Routing</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/routing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/routing/</guid>
      <description>Without the proper planning, even the best delivery operations will struggle to maintain efficiency and productivity. Organize your static routes or integrate with route optimization software and give your delivery operations the tools to be productive and cost efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitemap</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/sitemap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testimonials</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/testimonials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/testimonials/</guid>
      <description>Praesent commodo cursus magna, vel scelerisque nisl consectetur et. Maecenas sed diam eget risus varius blandit sit amet non magna. Cras justo odio, dapibus ac facilisis in, egestas eget quam. Vivamus sagittis lacus vel augue laoreet rutrum faucibus dolor auctor. Nulla vitae elit libero, a pharetra augue. Sed posuere consectetur est at lobortis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warehouse Management</title>
      <link>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/warehouse-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jkinley-sds.github.io/website-demo/software/features/warehouse-management/</guid>
      <description>Having a reliable and comprehensive Warehouse Management System is essential for any production or distribution company&amp;rsquo;s success. Leverage our built-in warehouse management functionality, or integrate with a dedicated enterprise WMS for even greater visibility into the movement and storage of your inventory.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>